Guide to the Laurence MacDaniels papers, [ca. 1915]-1986.
Laurence MacDaniels papers,
- Florida 1971 Answered Letters, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- MacDaniels Dictation, 1976-1978 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  Miscellaneous correspondence; Loose material: 1976-78 miscellaneous correspondence personal and business
- Attention 1976, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  Miscellaneous
- Miscellaneous Personal August 1976 Not Files, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  Miscellaneous correspondence, etc.
- Attention Feb.-Mar. 1977, 1977-02-1977-03 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  Miscellaneous material some correspondence
- 1976 Answered Correspondence Not Filed, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  Loose material: miscellaneous correspondence, etc.
- Ithaca - Shade Trees - Garbage 1969-71, 1969-1971 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Envelope - North American Lily Society - Wadekmper Letters, Date Unknown (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Correspondence 1972 - Need Not Answer Note 1973, 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  Miscellaneous correspondence including Lily, McGraw-Hill
- North American Lily Society 1973-4 Wadekmper, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Current September 1973, 1973-09 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  Miscellaneous correspondence, etc. - including lily seeds from Russia
- May June 1967 - Dec. 31, 67 File, 1967-05-1967-12-31 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  Miscellaneous correspondence including Gortzig
- Florida 1975 Miscellaneous, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Florida 1975 General File, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  Correspondence, etc.
- Current Mostly Personal 1964-65-66, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 35)
- Letters Current March April 1967, 1967-03-1967-04 (Box 13, Folder 36)
- Older Correspondence 1966, 1963-1975 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  Miscellaneous correspondence (1963); general nut culture; fluoridation; Yugoslavia; H. B. Tukey; R. M. Lewis; G. H. M. Lawrence; G. Slate; Northern Nut Growers Association; North American Lily Society; personal; Loose material: miscellaneous correspondence 1966-75
- Loose material: Elevation maps/charts - Cayuga and Seneca Lakes 1920-1964/1928-1964; miscellaneous correspondence / L. H. MacDaniels - Research Projects - General Plan, 1920-1964 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Correspondence regarding Canton bland vegetation; notes; Loose material: copy manuscript "Fruit Growing in the Patzcuaro Area" by LHM; Nature Conservancy correspondence, Cayuga Lake conservation material including newspaper clippings, etc.; Tompkins County Environmental Management Council newsletters
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association - Dr. Broad and Public Health Sanitary Code 1967-8, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Correspondence with Dr. Broad of Public Health regarding pollution of Cayuga Lake; correspondence with Frank Davenport of Cayuga Lake Basin Board regarding connection between CLBB and Cayuga Lake Preservation Association in problem of pollution of lake; open letter to cottage owners on Cayuga Lake; copy of Seneca Lake Watershed Regulations; copy Rules and Regulations for Protection from Contamination of Public Water Supply for Counties in New York State; miscellaneous notes, etc.; Loose material: Cayuga Lake Preservation Association - 1968-9 misc. correspondence, notes and newspaper clippings in envelope
- L. H. MacDaniels Cayuga Lake Preservation Association July 1972 Source Material, 1968-1972 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Meeting minutes; notes; correspondence Cooperative Extension material; Loose material: Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1968 newspaper clippings; meeting minutes; copy of manuscript "Summary List of Predicted Effects of a Nuclear Power Plant with Open-circuit Cooling System on Cayuga Lake"; copy of manuscript "Some Concerns About Environmental Impact of a Growing Nuclear Power Industry - Risks and Regulations"
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1968 Letters - Board Members, Tresurer, etc, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Current Source Material - Nov.-Dec. 1968, 1968-11-1968-12 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Notes, newspaper clippings; correspondence, pamphlets, etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1972 Recent Minutes and Letter to Secretary, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Correspondence; notes; copy of "Proposed Sanitary Code of Tompkins County Health District"; Cooperative Extension material; etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1967-8, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  Miscellaneous material
- Citizen's Committee Letters, etc. 1972, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  Regarding Cayuga Lake preservation
- New York State Federation of Lake Associations 1971, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Letters; newsletters; miscellaneous material regarding conservation in the Finger Lakes
- Pollution 1973 Nuclear and Others, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  Reprints from Congressional Record; pamphlets; copy of manuscript: Some Steps in Meeting Energy Shortage, etc.
- Ithaca City Council Etc., Trees - Reserve Material 1975 (1968-1975), 1968-1975 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  Material from Shade Tree Advisory Committee; correspondence; notes; etc.
- Shade Tree DeWitt Park 1975, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  Miscellaneous material regarding planting of shade trees
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Material, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Correspondence with New York State Electric and Gas; copy of Testimony Before the Committee on Environmental Protection and the General Welfare of the Council of the City of New York" 1970; miscellaneous material - regarding pollution of Cayuga Lake
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Newsletters 1973, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Loose material: Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1969-74 correspondence; newspaper articles
- Brush Burning - 1974, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Newspaper clippings; Loose material: General Conservation Material 1974 Circle Greenway; environmental management
- Environmental Management Council 1976, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  Meeting announcements and minutes; general published material
- File 1976, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  Correspondence with Rotary, Nature Conservancy material; Yugoslavia; Loose material: Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1972, notes and correspondence
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1973 Bell Station, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  Correspondence; newspaper articles; etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Flood Control 1973, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  Correspondence, copy: Temporary Greater Finger Lakes Basin Commission, etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Jan. Feb. 1973, 1973-01-1973-02 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  Miscellaneous material, copy: Environmental Quality Bond Act Factbook 1972, etc.
- (Manila Envelope) Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Flood Correspondence Etc. July-Aug. 1972 Burning Permits Etc., 1972-07-1972-08 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  General correspondence, etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Newsletter May 1973 Duplicate Material, 1973-05 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  Newspaper clippings, correspondence, etc.
- Fluoridation Important Basic, Date Unknown (Box 14, Folder 23)
  Correspondence, newspaper articles; Loose material: Shade Tree Advisory Committee Circle Greenway, notes, correspondence, copy: The Population Problem
- Atomic Generator Material for Barbara, Date Unknown (Box 14, Folder 24)
  Copy: New York Times Editorial: An Now... Welfare Island; copy: Some Concerns About Environmental Impact of a Growing Nuclear Power Industry I. The Discharge of Radioactive and Thermal Wastes: copy: The Impact of Nuclear Power on Air and Water Resources
- Loose material: The Preservation of Agricultural Land in New York - Report to Gov. Rockefeller From Commission on the Preservation of Agricultural Land. 1 copy and notes / Northern Nut Growers Association Testing 1974 - Data Cards and Letters Burns Bl. Wal., 1974 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Correspondence regarding walnuts et al.; schedules for scoring, notes, etc.
- Northern Nut Growers Association - Miscellaneous Material 1972-3 Letters and Tests Millikan-Haines, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Correspondence regarding general nut culture mostly black walnut, notes, scoring schedules, test blanks, letters from colwin Davis, R.T. Meister (Meister Publishing Co.), C. Haines, Millikan, etc., various reprints, etc.
- Bicentennial Aug. 1975-76, 1975-08-1976 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Newsletter
- Cayuga Lake Conservation Association 1975, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Miscellaneous material regarding - Cayuga Lake Conservation Association, report on Oswego River Basin, "Water Resources Development" Army Corps of Engineers; "Interboard Plan for the Greater Finger Lakes - Oswego River Basin by Regional Water Resources Planning Boards, etc.
- Coy Glen - Allan Treman Letter, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 5)
  Newspaper clippings, correspondence with A. H. Treman, report to membership of Cayuga Lake Preservation Association
- Greenway 1975 - Working Folder, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Copy of Proposed Revision of By-Laws of Tompkins County Environmental Management Council; fact sheet of official positions throughout New York State; Report and Recommendations Made to Tompkins County Environment Management Council September 1972 by Tompkins County Resource Development Committee, conservation Subcommittee, Greenbelt Working Group; highway map of Tompkins County, newspaper clippings
- EMC (Environmental Management Council) 1975, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  Index and status map 1975, Tompkins County Environment Management Council agendas, article on Nuclear Energy Parks in Pennsylvania and New York, meeting minutes, Work Program for Ithaca Waterways Study, newspaper clippings, Recent Proposed Legislation in New York State Dealing with Soil Conservation, notes, application and budget proposal - annual work program 1976-7 for Tompkins County Environment Management Council, annual report 1974 - Tompkins County Environment Management Council
- Environment - List of Organizations in Central New York and Ithaca, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  Directory and newsletter supplement to Ithaca Journal 1974 on organizations of Tompkins County
- CCCL Cayuga Lake Conservation 1974, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  Meeting minutes, report - Electric Generation Siting and the Environment, newspaper clippings
- L. H. MacDaniels - Cayuga Lake Conservation Association 1975, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  Meeting notices and minutes, by-laws of Cayuga Lake Conservation Association newsletter
- Clippings - 1974 March-April (envelope), 1974-03-1974-04 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  Environmental news
- Oswego River Basin - Dept. of the Army - 1975 (envelope), 1975 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  Published reports; Loose material: General Environmental and Conservation Material 1974-5-6 miscellaneous correspondence, copy: The 1975 Agricultural Conservation Program of Tompkins County, miscellaneous newspaper clippings, notes, bicentennial material, DeWitt Park, Men's Garden Club, correspondence with A. L. Adams, C. Gortzig
- Lick Brook - Area Photos - Negatives, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  Loose material Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Material 1972-3 newspaper clippings; general CLPA material, 2 copies Environmental Impact of Proposed Allan H. Treman State Marine Park - Oct. 25, 1973
- Environmental Management Council Minutes 1972-3, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Environmental Management Council Hamilton - Greenbelt Funding (envelope), 1970-12 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  Loose material: Tompkins County Area Recreation Demand Forecast and Facilities Choice Evaluation: An Analysis of the Recreation Potentials of Fall-Six Mile Creek Development December 1970.
- Greenbelt Minutes - File Copies 1972-3, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Environmental Management Council Active File 1972-3, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  Meeting minutes; copy: Report and Recommendations made to Tompkins County Environmental Management Council September 1972, correspondence - regarding federal funding; Loose material: Fluoride (1 folder), newspaper clippings, correspondence, etc.; Loose material: Water Pollution and Misc. (1 folder), miscellaneous material regarding water pollution, especially Cayuga Lake and local watersheds such as newspaper clippings Cayuga Lake Preservation Association material Tompkins County Environmental Management Council material, nuclear power plant proposition, energy shortage, article about 1816 freeze, etc.
- Nature Conservancy 1966 - Working Folder, 1966 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  Miscellaneous material, meeting notices and minutes, correspondence, membership lists, pamphlets, Policy and Procedure Manual 1963, etc.
- Federal Bills and Other Material Water Quality, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 19)
  Cayuga Lake Preservation Association - Mostly 1968 Duplicate and Other Pertinent Material
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association - Mostly 1968 Duplicate and Other Pertinent Material, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Clippings and Separates 1964-70, 1964-1970 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Relations with CCSCL, 1970 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  Copy: Statement Before the New York State conservation Sub-committee on Parks and Recreation June 1970, notes, correspondence, newspaper clippings; Loose material: Miscellaneous material notes on some conservation issue perhaps from phone call McKelvey, general environment
- Cayuga Lake Basin Board 1972, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  Correspondence, meeting notices, agendas, minutes
- Nature Conservancy 1972, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  Miscellaneous material; Loose material: Miscellaneous Tompkins County Environmental 1964-74, newspaper clippings, correspondence, Project Report of Environmental Management Council and Tompkins County Deptartment of Plannning, constitution and by-laws of Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Board of Directors Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1965
- Keuka Lake Shore Property Owners Incorporated, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 25)
  Newsletters, correspondence, constitution and by-laws, water levels, etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Important Men, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 26)
  List of nominees, open correspondence, newsletter, list of those interested in problems of Cayuga Lake
- Rotary Clubs 1965, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  Correspondence regarding Cayuga Lake Preservation Association
- Newsletters, Bulletins - Other Associations, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Koch [(Henry) Seneca Falls], 1962-09-1963-05 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  Correspondence September 1962-May 1963 between Henry Koch and G. Souhan and D. Morehouse
- Kiwanis Clubs, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  Ithaca Jay-Cees Roster 1963, correspondence
- George Souhan (New York), Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 31)
  Correspondence with Morehouse
- State, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  Draft Report: Preliminary Investigation of Problems in the Cayuga Water Shed 1963, procedures applying
- Lake Charts - Maps, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Planning - Cayuga Lake Preservation Association, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  Notes, outlines - membership drive blank 1963; notes on public hearing on creation of Cayuga Lake Regional Board
- Weeds, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 35)
  brochures on safe weed control
- Names, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 36)
  Cayuga Lake Preservation Association mailing list
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Constitution and By-Laws, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 37)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Meetings 1963-4, 1963-1964 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  notices and minutes of meetings
- Finger Lakes Association, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 39)
  mostly correspondence with George F. Train
- Finger Lakes Parks Commission, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  correspondence with William Pomeroy and G. G. Souhan ' 62
- Compass, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 41)
  correspondence with G. Souhan, D. Morehouse,O. Lee Duff
- B. Boat Club, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 42)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Carl Ayres
- Gould, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 43)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and G. Cramer of Gould Pump
- Gilfoil and McNeal - Syracuse, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 44)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Gilfoil and McNeal
- Lions Clubs, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 45)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Leland Henry
- Red Jacket Yacht Club, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 46)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Mary Headley
- Sylvania Electric Products, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 47)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and H. Wilcox of Sylvania
- Seneca Falls Penny-Saver, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 48)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Roger Chubb of Seneca Falls Penny-Saver
- Seneca County Board of Health, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 49)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Seneca County. Board of Health
- United States, Date Unknown (Box 15, Folder 50)
  correspondence with G. Souhan and Congressman Sam Stratton, D. Morehouse, Army Engineer R. S. Kelley
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1971 Meetings Minutes and Reserve Material, 1971 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  includes some correspondence, notes, newspaper clippings, reprints, manuscript "Cayuga Lake" published in Ithaca Journal Aug. 1971, L.H.M.
- Federation of Lake Associations 1972, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  includes list of members, memos to membership, reports on: Susquehanna River Basin Study 1970, Temporary State Commission on the Environmental Impact of Major Public Utility Facilities - 1970; Loose material: copy of World Federalist newsletter (1972?), various addresses, memo from H. Tukey (1967), newsletter from Cayuga Lake Preservation Association president (LHM) to members (1968), Environmental Directory for Tompkins County and Central NY, newsletter from U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (1972). note from J. G. Seeley, reprint of "Some Social Implications of the Scientific Method" (LHM 19401, miscellaneous pamphlets
- No Heading, Date Unknown (Box 16, Folder 3)
  song lists and words to songs not in LHM's handwriting
- Miscellaneous Material 1973, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  ranges from correspondence regarding nuclear plant on Cayuga Lake to newsletters from various conservation organizations; letter from G. Slate, R. M. Lewis of Cornell University Plantations
- Miscellaneous Material 1968, 1973, 1975, etc., 1968-1975 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  general conservation issues
- Miscellaneous Material 1966, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Miscellaneous 1968, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  correspondence, reprints, etc.
- Miscellaneous Material 1968, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  general conservation material mostly regarding pollution of Cayuga Lake, correspondence, meeting minutes, notes, etc.
- Miscellaneous Material 1968-69, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  general pollution material, Cayuga Lake notes, correspondence, etc. clippings - regarding Cayuga Lake Preservation Association
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Membership - Cayuga Lake Preservation Stationery 1968, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  correspondence, etc.
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Treasurer - Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1967, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  correspondence and financial reports
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Correspondence - Board of Directors, Other Than Secretary and Treasurer 1966-68, 1966-1968 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Minutes and Correspondence with George Cramer 1967, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Clippings Publicity 1967, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Material 1966-67, 1966-1967 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  mostly Cayuga Lake Preservation Association including meeting minutes and correspondence with G. Cramer
- Miscellaneous Material 1966, 1973, 1974, 1976, 1966-1976 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  very general collection of miscellaneous material; Bound copy: The Cayuga Lake Handbook Vol. I
- Miscellaneous Material 1978, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  some personal and other
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association Minutes Before 1970, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1970-71 Minutes Meetings, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1970-71 Letters (1968-69), 1968-1971 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  includes meeting minutes
- Cayuga Lake Preservation Association 1970-71 Reserve Material, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  meeting minutes, etc.
- Miscellaneous Material 1970, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  includes Cayuga Lake Preservation Association material, Rt. 13 and Rt. 96 propositions - Greenbelt Committee
- [envelope} Jane Marcham - Ithaca Journal Water Resources Eutrophication, Date Unknown (Box 16, Folder 23)
  3 published reports - regarding Eutrophication
- [envelope] Citizen's Committee To Save Cayuga Lake, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  Material Given Out By New York State Electric and Gas at Hearing 1968
- [envelope] Hennegen - Federation of Lake Associations 1970, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  published report, newsletters, memo to members of Federation
- Nature Conservancy Summer 1970, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  Includes meeting minutes, notes, general Nature Conservancy material
- [envelope] Gilbert Robison 1969, 1969 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  religious material
- [envelope] New York State Lake Associations 1970 Hennegen, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  some correspondence, mostly miscellaneous material
- [envelope] Suzanne Lehman - Postcards, Minutes, Etc. 1968-9, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  Cayuga Lake Preservation Association material
- Cayuga Lake Basin Board 1970-71, 1970-1971 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Copy Manuscript - "Waste" LHM, n.d., Date Unknown (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Advisory Council Greenbelt - Organization Material, 1970 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  newspaper clippings, membership lists (1970), notes, membership list of DeWitt Park Improvement Committee (1968), mailing list for Greenbelt (1970), Cayuga Lake Preservation Association notes, Tompkins County Environmental Management Council material, correspondence
- Miscellaneous Material, Conservation - Water, Date Unknown (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Greenbelt Correspondence and Older Material, Duplicate Memos 1968, 1968 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Greenbelt Report 1969-70, 72 Tompkins County Resource Conservation and Development Organization, 1969-1972 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Greenbelt Working Folder Mostly Older Material at Start of Project 1968-70, 1968-1970 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  correspondence, draft of proposal to town of Ithaca, notes, maps, etc.
- Miscellaneous Material - F and OH 1967, 1967 (Box 16, Folder 37)
- Pollination Studies 1925-26, 1925-1926 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  notes and graphs
- Pollination Manuscript 1928, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- [envelope] L. H. MacDaniels Pollination Data 1926, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  field notes, etc.
- Miscellaneous Pollination Correspondence 1926, 1926 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  F. S. Howlett, etc.
- Miscellaneous Pollination and Blooming Data 1929-30, 1929-1930 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  correspondence and notes
- Seed Count From Various Crosses 1928-29, 1928-1929 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  data and field notes including various manila envelopes containing data on different apple varieties, graphs
- [envelope] L. H. MacDaniels - Pollination Data 1930, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- American Society for Horticultural Sciences Publication - Pollination 1932 New Varieties, 1931-1932 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  data and field notes 1931-2
- Pollination Data Spring 1929, 1929 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Pollination Manuscript 1928-29, 1928-1929 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  correspondence, notes and data
- Pollination Data 1933, 1933 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Pollination Results 1931 Spring, 1931 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Pollination 1932, 1932 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  data and field notes
- Pollination 1937 Manuscript - Working Notes L. H. MacDaniels, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  draft of manuscript written with E. M. Hildebrand with notes, data and field notes
- Miscellaneous Pollen Germination and Other Data 1930, 1930 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  includes some correspondence, mostly notes
- [envelope] Pear Pollination 1928 Complete, 1928 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  Also Pollen Germination 1928